[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$500,000"], "LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "DT", "$", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "It's a pretty shameful moment, isn't it, for him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Well, I think it's incredibly shameful, but I think you're hitting on the things that I don't think he can ever take back, which is he went through the lengths, not simply of lying, but the litigiousness of suing the \"London Times\" for defamation, very expensive, winning a $500,000 judgment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "I don't see any way that he can do that, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Well, I mean, I've read that they might consider reinstating him in eight years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Given the scale of his betrayal to you personally, will you ever talk to him again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "But why would I ever believe anything he says to me or anyone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Let me -- let me update you as they're coming to this now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Pyrenees"]}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Is there any way back for Lance Armstrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Well, Piers, if he thought the climb up the Pyrenees was difficult, he's going to find the climb to regain his reputation is even worse.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Lance Armstrong"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Yes or no, did you ever take banned substances to enhance your cycling performance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Yes or no, was one of those banned substances EPO?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", ",", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Did you ever blood dope or use blood transfusions to enhance your cycling performance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Did you ever use any other banned substances like testosterone, cortisone, or human growth hormone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Yes or no, in all seven of your Tour de France victories, did you ever take banned substances or blood dope?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["France"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Seven times in a row?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Not in my opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "We're done with the yes and nos?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "We're done with the yes and nos.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Began when?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "For me or for --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'90s"]}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "For you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Mid-'90s.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "I mean, Christine, is -- in the Pantheon of sporting cheats, has anybody come close to Lance Armstrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "No, he's it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine", "Lance Armstrong"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "His lawyers have allowed him to do this, but just hearing those ramifications, knowing what I do about the lawsuits against British newspapers and so on, surely, he's going to be facing a battery of lawsuits, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Absolutely, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "WDT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Could he go to jail for perjury, for any of these confessions now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Well, it's not quite that simple.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "What do you feel for Lance Armstrong tonight on that level?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "I feel bad for him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Lance Armstrong"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What was the sort of overriding thing you learned about yourself that perhaps made you a better man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Well, what you have publicly displayed in this instance, is you aren't as good as you think you are and you're not as good as you act.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Do you expect widespread forgiveness?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Well, I mean, that's up for each individual to decide.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Beaufort"]}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "What do you see is missing that perhaps you can fill in terms of a gap?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "A buddy of mine from down in Beaufort I think summed it incredibly really well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Sanford"]}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "And so what I want to do is take what I've learned and hopefully apply it to again a great conundrum that now exists in Washington, which is how do we get our financial house in order?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, Mark Sanford, I wish you all the very best.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "What do we do about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, listen, I think the NRA is in a fundamentally different position than they were just 35 days ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Who's going to show some kind of political leadership?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Yes, you know, I have talked to so many of these parents and families over the last few weeks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Mr. Elder, no gun problem in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Piers, thank you very much for having me on.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Elder"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Claim?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Yes, it's a claim.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Heritage Foundation"]}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "So how do you explain that using your argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Piers, this has been studied many times by organizations like the Heritage Foundation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "How do you explain it's not happening in New York?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "There are lots of factors why people commit crimes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "JJS", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "These are things you should consider, aren't they, before you dismiss there being no gun problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "LDER: They most certainly are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mardi Gras"], "LOCATION": ["New Orleans"], "PERSON": ["Ms. Romak"]}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "What is this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "This is a Mardi Gras king cake that was sent by Ms. Romak (ph) from New Orleans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "So, I mean, look, I straddle the line and sometimes I -- you can't help but wonder, is this the right path or is this the right path?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "I think it's been so the right path for you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "When you hear this debate -- it's an interesting debate, I think, about whether you should have armed security in school, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "I don't like -- this is my personal opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "I'm very, very frustrated with this story.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Lance Armstrong"]}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "You do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "I think Lance Armstrong will go down in history as the greatest sporting cheat of them all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "EX", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "As a survivor, can you divorce what he has done as a survivor to help cancer and other charities, and the money he has raised, from everything we now know about him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Look, I know how much need there is for money and for research and for things for cancer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Is there such a thing as bad money when it comes to fundraising for charity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I think there can be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "How are you dealing with no alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "It's depressing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Calm everyone down a bit, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "Why did you come up with the idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "I thought it was a lot of people were in a funk, you know, whether it's tragedies around the world or close to home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "He's just become a grandfather.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "Look, I think that it's one of those things that you wonder who is going to be wearing the bib at the end, the grandchild or Charlie Sheen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "I think Charlie probably feels pretty damn relieved he made it to be a grandfather.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "Is that always the demon on your shoulder?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]